Today, you have proven
yourselves among the elite!
And we, the Academy Knights, welcome you!
As you know, I am the captain
of said knights, Loretta Kugrit.
Some of you already know
my younger sister, Loretta.
She happens to be a
first-year like yourselves!
Oh, yeah!
She's one half of
Miskler's minibus squadron!
What is a minibus?
I'm the vice-captain, Lambert
Aurousseau, at your service.
It's a pleasure to meet you!
And Lambert here is Lene's elder brother.
Let's dive right into our first
order of business, shall we?
Planning the Foundation Day Fair!
The old FDF, huh?
And what exactly are we knights
going to do for the big day?
Well, we typically run a
cafe and serve customers.
You'll be knights in dining armor!
If I have to touch people's dirty
plates like some common servant girl,
I am literally going to die.
A regular cafe does sound a little boring.
Maybe we could add some kind of theme.
It's never a good sign
when he gets creative.
A cafe does not need a theme.
What do you think, Ray?
Any suggestions?
Uh, let me think.
I guess we could go basic and
do a maid cafe or a butler cafe.
Except there's nothing novel about
having a servant in this world.
And I have no interest in sexy butlers.
Although I would like to see Miss
Claire in a butler's uniform.
Oh, now there's an idea.
What if we draw people in with a gimmick
where the guys and girls swap styles?
Hold on, when you say styles,
do you mean the ladies will dress
as butlers and we'll dress as maids?
Exactly.
The same basic cafe that we all know and
love, but with a delightfully quirky twist.
I appreciate your vision,
but would it be acceptable for
royals to participate in that?
Hm?
Why would it be a problem?
Oh, where do I even begin?
You're overthinking it.
Besides, Rod's keen on the idea,
so let's let him have this one.
Don't tell me you support this!
I think I'd like to experiment
with dressing up as a girl.
Sounds like fun.
If Prince Hugh votes yes,
then I do too. Misha?
Miss Claire in men's clothes?
Good God, yes.
I support you too, Prince Rai.
You do not get a vote,
you lascivious creature.
I should have known you'd do this.
Miss Claire,
don't you think that Prince Thane would
look adorable in a frilly maid uniform?
Imagine the magnificence.
Got him again.
Well then, any objections?
I'm 100 % against this idea.
Voting has been closed, Captain!
Yes!
Then our festival project for this year
is officially a cross-dressing cafe!
Yes, I know, no, I'm a pride
What you want? Say it again
All I want, only you?
Don't you know, you're a fool?
You're a fool, you're a fool.
Hey, you're a fool, you're a fool.
I can't believe you,
you won't believe you!
Or you won't believe me.
I can't believe you, you won't believe me.
I can't believe you, it's not an event.
So I'll raise your hand.
Now, the joy of happiness is equal.
The secret is just one thing.
Come from the heart.
Raise your hand, let's do it.
Raise your hand, if you're off.
Rei-chan-han, more i-kai!
Rei-chan-han, i-i-se-kai!
I don't want to give up until I die!
I love you, I love you!
It's not too late to voice my opposition.
Miss Claire.
Thank you for being such a
good friend to my sister.
Lene's spoken very highly
of you as well, Ray Taylor.
Thank you, Master Lambert.
I've heard that you're a
pretty good egg yourself.
Really?
You've heard of him before today?
He's the magic tool specialist
who takes care of the
Academy's maintenance and
inspection single-handedly.
He's a renowned inventor
too, right, Master Lambert?
I haven't done anything all that special.
But I wondered if I might
ask a favor of you two.
We've been noticing a lot more
conflicts between students recently.
Now that you mention it,
some of the commoners have been
behaving strangely as of late.
Right.
And a number of small fights
have broken out because of it.
Goodness, how unfortunate.
The captain and I have had our hands
full dealing with the altercations.
I'm hoping you could investigate
some other matters for us.
What do you think?
Don't you know who I am?
No matter what the occasion,
I shall rise to it flawlessly!
I certainly appreciate it. Go on, then.
What are the other matters
you need help with?
Well, you see, rumor has
it campus is haunted.
Apparently,
some students have reported seeing a
suspicious figure wandering the halls at night.
Some see it in the stairway.
Or in the kitchen.
And when the students who were on night
patrol attempted to approach the figure
Later on a wet spot in the shape of a
handprint was discovered on their shoulders
Why Miss Claire you're looking
a little pale over there
could it be that you're
afraid of Not another word you
goblin I fear nothing do you
hear me oh my it seems I've
hit a sore spot would you
prefer to do a different task?
I mean, we've got cafe prep to do!
But if the kitchen is full of coolies?
then that might be out, too.
Well, so far, there have
only been sightings.
It hasn't damaged anything yet.
I'll just cover our eyes
if we see something.
It is the Knight's solemn duty to
protect the Academy's students!
It would be wrong to ignore any
disturbance, however trivial!
Oh, what are you saying, Miss Claire?
I am saying, let the vile specter come!
I shall be the most noble ghost
hunter this world has ever known!
And that is how my spooktacular
evening with Ms. Claire began.
Target location has been reached.
I'll go scope out the
prep room in the back.
Can you stay here where it's
light and keep a lookout?
Did you really just get
me an order, commoner?
Sorry.
You can go to the back room if you want
No, I shall let it go this time, but
don't you dare let it happen again.
All right, let's bust a ghost
Ghosts are real ghosts are not real
Of course they aren't real.
How absurd.
Those foolish students
must have been half asleep.
Are you okay?
What happened?
Look, my hand is covered in goop. Hmm.
Oh, you're right.
It looks like some kind of gelatin.
What is it?
Have I been attacked by a ghost?
Probably nothing to worry about, but
we'll send it in for analysis to be sure.
I was covered in something sticky.
Why are you so calm?
You'll be fine with some soap and water.
Why don't you just hang out here
until I finish exploring the back?
Those presumptuous
academy knights forcing me
to spend the night here
like a scullery maid!
What if ghosts are real?
What if there's one here right now?
Hello, Miss Squire!
For you, madame.
Wait, what am I looking at?
It is good fondant au chocolat.
It's sort of like a chocolate
cake, but better and gooier.
But where on earth did you get this?
You really expect me to believe you managed
to acquire a cake made from chocolate?
Brumet's exclusive new confection?
Explain yourself!
You could get bogged down in the details,
or you could just take a bite
and tell me what you think.
Fine.
I'll have you know I'm not easily
impressed, but I'll try it.
It's delicious!
The cake is so rich in chocolate flavor,
and more chocolate oozes
out with every bite.
Why, it's positively heavenly!
Commoner, I must meet the
patissier who concocted this!
Wait, hold on.
Are you saying you made this cake?
I've been coming up with all kinds of
scrumptious recipes to make for you.
How do you find time
to fiddle about in the
kitchen when you're always at my service?
Wait,
a suspicious figure that
shows up night after night,
wandering the halls, haunting the kitchen!
Don't tell me!
You're the ghost we've been hunting for!
Am I spooky enough?
Why didn't you tell me
instead of letting me suffer?!
I wanted to surprise you!
Dede!
I made his food in a
nice cozy spot to sleep.
She's been planning it.
Wait, what is this?
Why did you only bring one cot?
It's like a slumber party!
Things have taken a
turn for the ridiculous.
I'm leaving as soon as I finish my cake.
Aw, you're really not gonna
spend the night with me?
Of course I'm not!
And we've already solved the
mystery of the fake ghost!
Huh?
But, um, what about
the handprints, though?
I genuinely don't know
where they came from.
Enough games!
I'm not a fool!
And I won't fall for your tricks again!
I'm not kidding, though. Oh, stop it!
I'm going back to my
room! Wait! Miss Claire!
Assistant, go save me!
Oh, Ray Lair!
What? Ray Lair?
Whatcha doing, girl?
Did you follow me here?
Wait, the handprint.
How long that was... her? Oh yeah!
Ray Lair's on a transforming kick!
I am done. Goodbye.
Aww, we were gonna cuddle!
So, um, does this mean you're not leaving?
I would have, but I'm exhausted
from all your nonsense.
What's wrong?
Don't just stand there.
Are you getting in or not?
It's cold.
Could you scoot a little closer?
Touch me, and I will smother
you in your sleep! Hurry!
Try there!
You have to stay on the side!
Mother? Hello?
Where are you?
I don't want to sleep by myself tonight!
I feel so frightened!
Mother, please!
Ms. Clare?
Lene?
I'm sorry, but your mother
won't be returning home tonight.
And the Master is still
busy with work, I'm afraid.
Oh...
No!
I don't want you to leave!
You and Father have to
stay with me always!
I'm so sorry, my love, but it's
past time for us to be on our way.
But you can't go now!
Today's my birthday!
What's so important that
you have to leave me?
Oh, Claire.
Come now, Claire.
Show your mother some grace.
As nobles, we must put our
duties before all else.
I know, but you always tell me to be
patient when you leave, and I have been.
I've become really good at it, so
I thought maybe just this once.
I'm sorry, dear.
Truly, I am.
But I'll make this up to you, I promise.
Oh, I know.
I'll buy you a special birthday present.
You can choose whatever you want.
What would you like?
No, forget it!
I don't want a present!
I hate you! Claire!
Amelia.
A very happy birthday to you, Ms. Clare.
May there be many more to come.
This is for you.
We all work together to
pick something special.
Wow it's pretty but I
think it might be too big
for me to use right now
you may need some time to
grow into it but until
that happens I think it
might be nice if you used
it to brush Lady Melia's
That's a great idea!
I'm gonna do that!
Now then, shall we sit down to dinner?
Ms. Claire! Ms. Claire!
I have terrible news, Ms. Claire!
Please open up!
What?
Your parents were in a carriage accident.
Lady Melia, what?
Miss Claire, you should try
to at least eat something.
I'm worried that you'll get sick.
Maybe if I die, I'll
get to see Mother again.
How could you say such a thing?
Lady Melia would be so
sad if she heard you!
Before she left, I told my
mother that I hated her.
We were fighting, and that was
the last thing I ever said to her.
Why did I say that?
What's wrong with me?
I didn't get to tell her that I was sorry.
I'm sorry, Mother.
Oh, I almost forgot.
I talked with Master
Lambert for a bit yesterday.
Oh, you did?
Yeah, he's a stand-up gent.
He's kind and reliable and very humble.
even though he's super talented.
He really is.
And did you know, along with
his magic tool research,
he's also learning how
monsters become familiars?
They made him vice-captain
because of how...
Anyway, I'm so proud
to call him my brother.
Sure, who wouldn't be?
So, would you mind helping us with
prep for the Foundation Day Fair?
Well, I think Master Lambert
would appreciate it. Yeah?
Oh, this looks quite delicious.
So this is the top pick for our
menu at the Foundation Day Fair?
Yep, go on and taste it.
Thank you for the food.
It's good.
This flavor, it tastes familiar.
Oh, I know what it is.
This must be mayonnaise.
It's the new sauce that was
just released by Brumet.
So delicious.
Right on the mail, Miss Claire.
It's from Broom, eh?
How did you get something like that?
Uh, well, uh, I heard about it
and then tried making my own.
Try these ones next, okay?
Using limited ingredients
really makes the meat stand out.
Yes, I must admit, you're quite
the chef for a lowly commoner. Hmm.
Ray, may I ask you something? Hmm?
You wouldn't happen to be the one supplying
all of these new recipes to Brumet now,
would you?
Because of the whole mayonnaise thing?
That was just...
You can't fool me.
I know it's next to impossible to guess a
recipe like that after hearing about it.
The ingredients, the texture, the taste.
Why would it take a culinary
genius to get them all just right?
Uh, oh, stop it!
You're bothering me!
Tell me about the meat, then.
Is rare meat on sandwiches
a Brumet innovation as well?
Oh, that wasn't just rare meat.
It's actually called rosé, and it looks
like that because the myoglobin is...
Oh, crap.
Caught by a true foodie.
Might as well spill some of the beans.
Okay, you're right.
I've secretly been giving my recipes
to Brumet to put on their menu.
It's common sense to utilize skills
from a previous life to turn a profit.
Brumet is the only upscale restaurant in
this country, so the payoff was massive.
Fun fact, chocolate was the
first recipe I sold them.
But please, promise me that you'll
keep this between you and me.
I don't get it.
Being the Taliban, Brumet's
menu is impressive.
Why hide it?
I can't tell you all the details.
Just know it's for Miss Claire.
Wait, what do you mean?
Afraid I can't say.
Just please don't tell her.
I mean, we all have a few
secrets, don't we, Lene?
I suppose so.
But in return, will you promise
to teach me one of your recipes?
If you want.
Yes.
I want to make something
good for Miss Claire.
Okay, meet me here again tonight.
So you decided to bring
Miss Claire with you.
Did I interrupt your secret club?
If you two are planning to make
something, then you are in luck.
I'll lend you my palate as a taste tester.
What the heck?
I told you not to tell her anything!
I'm sorry.
I was just so excited.
Nothing I can do now.
Put this on.
I think it's chilly at night.
Let us know if you need something heavier.
Hurry up and cook something. Okay!
Tonight we have the crème brûlée.
It's delicious!
You've really outdone
yourself this time, Rei.
It's even richer than regular custard.
The caramelized sugar on top is exquisite!
Would you mind getting me some tea, Lene?
Coming up!
Hey, Lene.
For you.
Ray, is this a recipe for mammoth?
Memorize it, and then ditch the note.
It's insurance.
Okay?
I just really want you to have
this, in case you ever need it.
I will need to sample this
again. What? You want another?
Miss Claire, that's a lot of sugar.
It's okay.
I'd recommend whipping up another
batch for practice anyway.
Are you okay?
Yes, just burn myself a little.
My, you're quite the healer.
You two seem awfully close.
Why, Miss Clara, are you jealous?
Oh, I don't know what you're saying.
What exactly do you think I'd be
jealous of, you impertinent insect?
Here we go again.
On days like this, I'm reminded that even
when nothing major happens, I'm so lucky.
I just wish this happiness
could last forever.
But I know better than that.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
You have to read this. Be
delicious. Be delicious.
Love, love. Squee, squee. I love you. Huh!
What in the world is this?
It's the moment you've
all been waiting for!
The Foundation Day Fair!